Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 1987-2011; 11; 6.4 cubic ft.
  - Interfaith Coalition Event, 2003 September 23 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Image of A. Bonowitz at Amnesty International Event, ca. 1995 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - J. D. Scott Execution Protest, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Journey of Hope Events, 2004 March 28 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Journey of Hope Events, 2004 May 4 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Journey of Hope Events, 2004 May 4 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Journey of Hope Events, 2004 May 4 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Journey of Hope Events, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Journey of Hope Indiana/ Kentucky, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Journey of Hope Negatives, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Journey of Hope - Speaker Event, 2003 October 13-14 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope Time Out On Executions, 2004 May 3-4 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope Time Out On Executions, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Juan Melendez Event, 2005 September (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Life Over Death Party, 2005 September (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Lobbying, 2011 January (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Loose Group Photos of A. Bonowitz, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Louisville Event, 2003 April (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Melendez Tour, 2005 April 19 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Melendez Tour, 2003 May 18-21 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - "Moratorium Now!" Signage, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Event, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - NCADP, 2003 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - NCADP, 2003 April (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - NCADP Event, 2004 October 26 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - NCADP Event, 2004 October 26 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - NCADP Event, 2004 October 26 (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - NCADP Event, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - NCADP Event, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - NCADP Rally, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Negatives, Undated (Box 2 (11-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Negatives, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Negatives, 2005 March 7 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Negatives, 2004 March 3 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - New Mexico Journey of Hope, 2004 May 3 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - New Mexico Journey of Hope, 2004 May 3 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - North Carolina Journey of Hope, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Ohio Journey of Hope for McVeigh Execution, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Ohio Protest, 2005 September 27 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Peace Rally, 2001 September 20 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Journey of Hope, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Journey of Hope, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1995 March 21 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 2000 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 2000 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 2000 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Photographs, 2001 July (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Photographs, 2001 October 18 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Photographs, 2001 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Photographs, 2005 March 7 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 2005 July 1 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 2005 July 5 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Photographs, 2005 July 2-4 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 2005 August 27 (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (11-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Undated (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Photo CD, 2001 January 16 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Photo CD, 2001 July (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Photo CD, 2002 May 8 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Photo CD, 2002 July 29 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Photo CD, 2002 September 15 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Photo CD, 2002 July 29 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Photo CD, 2002 October 11 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Photo CD, 2002 October 11 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Photo CD, 2002 October 13 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Photo CD, 2002 November 3 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Photo CD, 2002 November 3 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Photo CD, 2002 November 3 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Photo CD, 2002 November 3 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Photo CD, 2002 November 3 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Photo CD, 2002 November 3 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Photo CD, 2003 April 22 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Photo CD, 2003 May 16 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Photo CD, 2003 May 21 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Photo CD, 2003 June 15 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Photo CD, 2003 July 28 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Photo CD, 2003 October 13-14 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Photo CD, 2003 December 15 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Photo CD, 2004 November 10 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Photo CD, 2003 December 15 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Photo CD, 2004 July 15 (Box 4 (11-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Photo CD, 2004 October 26 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Photo CD, 2004 December 15 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Photo CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Photo CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Photo CD, 2002 May 6 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Photo CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Photo CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Photo CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Photo CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Photographs on CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Photo CD and Negatives, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Photographs and Note From Unknown Sender, 2001 June 12 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Photographs from Kathy Harris, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disk, 1998 May (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Photos on Floppy Disk, 2000 November (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Photos on Floppy Disk, 2000 November (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disks, 2001 October 18 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disks, 2000 November (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Pictures on Floppy Disk, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disks, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disk, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disks, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disk and CD, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Photographs on Floppy Disk, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Photos Provided for Documentary, 1998 November 13 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Protest Against Execution of Glen Ocha, 2001 April 5 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Protest Against Execution of John Blackwelder, 2004 May 26 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Protest Images Photo CD, 2003 April 22 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Protest Poster Images, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Rachel King Negatives Contact Sheet, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - "Rally at Tally" Florida Moratorium Walk, 2002 January 31 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Sam Reece Sheppard Event Enlarged Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Sam Sheppard Civil Trial, 2000 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Sam Sheppard Photographs on Floppy Disk, Undated (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Spring Break Event, 2005 March 19 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Spring Break Event, 2005 March 19 (Box 5 (11-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Starvin for Justice, 1999 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Starvin for Justice, 2001 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Starvin for Justice, 2005 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Starvin for Justice, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Starvin for Justice, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - State College Event Set-Up, 1998 May 29 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - State of the World Forum Photographs, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Steve Earle, Journey of Hope Photographs, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Stop Executions Postcard Images, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Stop Executions Supreme Court Protest, 1997 January 17 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Supreme Court Fast and Vigil, 2004 July 15 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Supreme Court Protest, 1997 January (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Supreme Court Protest, 1997 January (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Supreme Court Protest and Arrest, 1997 January 17 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Supreme Court Protest Negatives, 1997 January 17 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Terre Haute Journey of Hope, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - TCADP/ Steve Earle Event, 2005 February 1 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Texas Journey of Hope, 1998 January (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Texas Journey of Hope, 2005 April 20 (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Time Out on Executions, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Time Out on Executions, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Time Out on Executions, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Time Out on Executions, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Unsorted Negatives, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Unsorted Negatives, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Unsorted Negatives, Undated (Box 6 (11-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Unsorted Photographs, 1987-1996 (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Unsorted Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Unsorted Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Unsorted Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Unsorted Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Unsorted Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Unsorted Photographs, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Virginia Beach Protest, 2003 November 11 (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Walk for Justice, 1999 September 25 (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Walk for Justice, 1999 September 25 (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Walk for Justice, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Walk for Justice, Undated (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Warped Tour Abolution Booth, 2003 July (Box 7 (11-Photographs), Folder 13)
- Audio Visual Materials, 1977-2013; 12; 3.79 cubic ft.
  This series contains electronic copies of documents, computer backups, documentaries, interviews, recorded conferences and events, and recorded news reports and specials. The formats included are audio tapes, one beta tape, CDs/DVDs, 3. 5 floppy discs, mini DV tapes, one USB drive, VHS tapes, and zip disks. Several of the materials are unlabeled. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - 143 Miles, Undated (Oversized 5, Vhs 16)
  - 3150 PC E-mail Download, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 12)
  - 3150 Pre Email [1 of 2], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 17)
  - 40 Jahre Fur die Menschenrechte, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 2)
  - 48 Hours Mystery "Grave Injustice", 2011 April 23 (Oversized 6, Cd 3)
  - 70x7 the Forgiveness Equation - Justice Productions, 2008 (Oversized 6, Cd 4)
  - 70x7 the Forgiveness Equation - Justice Productions, 2009 (Oversized 6, Cd 5)
  - A Culture of Life and the Penalty of Death, 2006 (Oversized 6, Cd 8)
  - A Day - Cabina v. Miller, 1993 March 1 (Oversized 7, Cassette 1)
  - A View From the Underside, The Legacy of Dietrich Bonhoeffer, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 60)
  - AAC Zipfile, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 6)
  - ABA Report Materials, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 1)
  - Abe at 3150 Computer WP 5.1 [1 of 4], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 13)
  - Abe at 3150 Computer WP 5.1 [2 of 4], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 14)
  - Abe at 3150 Computer WP 5.1 [3 of 4], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 15)
  - Abe at 3150 Computer WP 5.1 [4 of 4], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 16)
  - Abe Bonowitz 4-11, Undated (Oversized 7, Cassette 2)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute Documents, 2012 November (Oversized 7, Usb 1)
  - Abu-Ali Abdur'rahman Clemency Video, 2002 March 13 (Oversized 1, Vhs 1)
  - American Bar Association Executing Justice: Call for a Moratorium on Executions, Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 2)
  - Amnesty International USA AGM '96 Opening Ceremonies - Sr. Diana Ortiz, 1996 (Oversized 1, Vhs 3)
  - Anthony Apanovitch "A Second Look", Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 4)
  - Backup, 1999 June (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 48)
  - Backup, 2000 August 26 (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 49)
  - Backup, 1999 January 26 (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 50)
  - Backup, 1998 November 7 (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 44)
  - Backup Main Computer, 2001 October 3 (Oversized 7, Cd 14)
  - Balancing the Scales - Texas Moratorium Network, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 7)
  - Balancing the Scales - Texas Moratorium Network, Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 5)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Cd 12)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 1)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 2)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 23)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 28)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 30)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 1)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 14)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 15)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 16)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 17)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 18)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 19)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 20)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Mini-dv 21)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 22)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 23)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 24)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 25)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 26)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 27)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 32)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 46)
  - Blank, Undated (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 53)
  - Blank VHS Tape, Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 6)
  - Bonus Video from Andrew Mason! Promoting Peace on Earth and Goodwill to All, Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 7)
  - Bringin' Abolition Day, Undated (Oversized 7, Cassette 3)
  - Bumper Sticker Cell Intake Sheet, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 18)
  - Cesar Chavez, The Hispanic and Latin American Heritage, 1995 (Oversized 1, Vhs 8)
  - Chavez Directions, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 38)
  - Children's Crusade to Death Row, 1997 August 18 (Oversized 1, Vhs 9)
  - Common Man Uncommon Vision, The Cesar Chavez Story, Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 10)
  - Community Relations in Wake of Murder, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 2)
  - Copy of Cards, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 32)
  - C-Span National Conference on Civil Disobedience, Undated (Oversized 1, Vhs 11)
  - CUADP [disc 1 of 2], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 10)
  - CUADP [disc 2 of 2], Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 8)
  - CUADP Computer Backup, 2002 July (Oversized 7, Cd 11)
  - CUADP Computer Backup, 2002 July (Oversized 7, Cd 13)
  - Dateline about John Grisham Nonfiction Work "The Accused", Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 9)
  - Dead Man Walking, The Journey Continues, 2005 September 7 (Oversized 6, Cd 10)
  - Death Penalty Newsclips, 1999-2000 (Oversized 1, Vhs 12)
  - Death Penalty Resources for Communities of Faith - Death Penalty Information Center, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 12)
  - Death Penalty: Unspoken, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 11)
  - Do 1, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 3)
  - Do 2, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 4)
  - Do 3, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 5)
  - Do 4, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 6)
  - Donation Back-Up, 2005 March 31 (Oversized 6, Cd 13)
  - E1, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 37)
  - E10, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 33)
  - E13, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 40)
  - E2, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 27)
  - E3, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 43)
  - E5, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 36)
  - E6, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 42)
  - E7, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 41)
  - E8, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 35)
  - E9, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 34)
  - Elements of Power M. Abdulmalik - Islam on Campus, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 14)
  - ELL, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 11)
  - Ethical Culture, 2005 (Oversized 1, Vhs 13)
  - Eudora, 2001 January 9 (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 52)
  - Eudora Backup, 2000 December 1 (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 51)
  - Evening with Sister Helen Prejean, 1996 September 22 (Oversized 7, Cassette 4)
  - Execution of Gary Graham, Undated (Oversized 2, Vhs 1)
  - Execution Vigil, Lucasville, Ohio, 2005 March 8 (Oversized 6, Cd 15)
  - Executions, Undated (Oversized 2, Vhs 2)
  - Exonerated: They Survived Death Row, 2005 July 28 (Oversized 2, Vhs 3)
  - Fast & Vigil by Scott Langely, 2006 (Oversized 6, Cd 17)
  - Fearless Heart Steve Earle, 2000 October 20 (Oversized 2, Vhs 4)
  - Files Backup, 1998 April 15 (Oversized 8, Zip-disk 45)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Bud Welch, Undated (Oversized 2, Vhs 5)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Carolyn McVeigh, Undated (Oversized 2, Vhs 6)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Interviews and Meetings in Tallahassee [1 of 3], 2001 April 7 (Oversized 2, Vhs 7)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Interviews and Meetings in Tallahassee [1 of 3], 2001 April 7 (Oversized 2, Vhs 8)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Interviews and Meetings in Tallahassee [2 of 3], 2001 April 7 (Oversized 2, Vhs 9)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Interviews and Meetings in Tallahassee [2 of 3], 2001 April 7 (Oversized 2, Vhs 10)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Interviews and Meetings in Tallahassee [3 of 3], 2001 April 7 (Oversized 2, Vhs 11)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Interviews and Meetings in Tallahassee [3 of 3], 2001 April 7 (Oversized 2, Vhs 12)
  - Foridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Press Conference in Tallahassee, 2003 January 30 (Oversized 2, Vhs 13)
  - Fox Dayside - Abe v. Clements on Paul Hill, 2003 September 3 (Oversized 2, Vhs 14)
  - Freedom: Songs About Human Rights, Undated (Oversized 7, Cassette 5)
  - Furnature Store Shoot Out and "A Matter of Life & Death", Undated (Oversized 2, Vhs 15)
  - George, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 7)
  - Holler to the Hood, 2003 (Oversized 6, Cd 18)
  - Human Life Belongs to God, Talking About the Death Penalty - Developed by the Florida Catholic Conference, 2002 August (Oversized 3, Vhs 1)
  - In the Shadow of Landmines America's Defense Monitor Presents Landmine Survivors Media Project, 2000 January 22 (Oversized 3, Vhs 2)
  - Interview with an Executioner: A Documentary, Undated (Oversized 3, Vhs 3)
  - Inventory - JH, 1998 May 28 (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 31)
  - ISLAM: What Everyone Should Know About It., Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 19)
  - Journey of Hope Demo, Undated (Oversized 3, Vhs 4)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas [1 of 2], 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 5)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas [2 of 2], 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 6)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas, Adopted Daughter Murdered, 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 7)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas, Adopted Daughter Murdered, 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 8)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas, Awards Ceremony, 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 9)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas, Awards Ceremony, 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 10)
  - Journey of Hope, Austin, Texas, No Silence No Shame, 2005 Octobe (Oversized 3, Vhs 11)
  - Journey of Hope, Murder Victims' Families for Reconcilliation, Undated (Oversized 2, Vhs 31)
  - Journey of Hope, Not in My Name, 1995 (Oversized 3, Vhs 12)
  - Journey of Hope, Richmond, Virginia, 2006 October (Oversized 3, Vhs 13)
  - Juan Melendez, 2008 (Oversized 6, Cd 20)
  - Juan Melendez, 2008 (Oversized 6, Cd 21)
  - Keith LaMar, Condemned, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 22)
  - Ken Nordines Word Jazz, 1993 August 26 (Oversized 7, Cassette 6)
  - Lantern Backup, 1993 January 17 (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 24)
  - Lantern Backup, 1993 January 17 (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 25)
  - Late Night Phone Conversation, Undated (Oversized 9, Mini-dv 28)
  - Lawyers Against the Death Penalty "Prisoner", Undated (Oversized 3, Vhs 14)
  - Lethal Injustice Do What you Can - Jake, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 29)
  - Mailing List, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 20)
  - Main Mail, Undated (Oversized 8, Floppy-disk 22)
  - Malingering Mental Illness, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 23)
  - Malingering Mental Illness, Undated (Oversized 6, Cd 24)
  - March for Abolition, Terre Haute, Indiana, Undated (Oversized 3, Vhs 15)
  - McVeigh, Undated (Oversized 7, Mini-dv 8)
  - McVeigh Execution, Undated (Oversized 4, Vhs 1)
  - Moment of Dawn, 1995 (Oversized 7, Cassette 7)